(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Sandy and I were opposites.
Sandy was pretty.
I was ugly.
Sandy was dumb.
I was smart.
Sandy's parents were divorced.
My parents have been married for 30 years.
Sandy was athletic.
I was clumsy.
Sandy was shy.
I was loud.
Sandy was liked by everyone.
Some people hated me.
Sandy was funny.
Everyone laughed at her jokes.
I couldn't even tell a joke.
Sandy was clean.
I was dirty.
We were very different, obviously, but we were
still friends.
We have been friends since first grade.
We will go to the same college.
We won't be roommates, though.
I guess what they say is true.
Opposites really do attract.